hardwareandtools.com 2008-12-18

# HardwareAndTools.com: Privacy Policy

|    

|  |  |   
---|---|---  
  
* * *

**Add items above to your shopping cart and these special prices will appear automatically**  
  
Privacy Policy

  * Information We Gather
  * Checkout and Order Forms
  * Cookies
  * Security
  * Opt Out Newsletters
  * General Advice
  * Amendments

HardwareAndTools.com is a trade name of Hardware and Tools Corp. This privacy statement demonstrates our firm commitment to privacy and to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the Webmaster by emailing [webmaster@hardwareandtools.com](mailto:webmaster@hardwareandtools.com)

## Information We Gather

Our websites log IP addresses and browser types, but we do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that users sessions are tracked, but users remain anonymous. You can browse our site without entering any personal information and therefore remain anonymous during your visit. We hope our visitors will register so that we can learn more about our visitors. Our order/registration form asks users for name, email, address, preferences, and some limited demographic information. This information is needed to rapidly process and ship your order. 

We maintain a list of email addresses to send our newsletters containing special offers you may be interested in. If you prefer not to receive the newsletter, but would still like to register, you may register and opt out of our newsletter. Certain specials and bonus gifts will be available only with coupons included in the free newsletter. 

Back to Top

* * *

## Checkout and Order Forms

The information that we require on our order form is used to process your orders quickly and accurately. Your contact information is used to send you the product that you purchase and your billing information will only be used to bill you for that product.  We do not sell or distribute email, addresses or telephone numbers, except to the carriers involved in delivering your packages to facilitate tracking and delivery.

Back to Top

* * *

## Cookies

Our site uses cookies to keep track referrals and items in your shopping cart and wish list. We also use cookies to remember members passwords so you do not have to re-enter them each time they visit the site. You can set your browser to reject cookies, however, if certain cookies that track your selections are rejected, we won't be able to keep items in your cart from visit to visit. You will have to reenter this information on every visit.

Back to Top

* * *

## Security

When you place an order online, your personal information and credit card information are scrambled using encryption technology before being sent over the Internet. This makes it virtually impossible for your information to be stolen or intercepted while being transferred through cyberspace. When we receive your order, it is kept encrypted behind a firewall until we're ready to process it. In addition, we erase most of your credit card information from our web site database so it is therefore safe from "hackers."

Back to Top

* * *

## Opt Out Newsletters

If at any time after registering, you change your mind about receiving the newsletter or sharing your information with third parties, you may visit the site and unsubscribe automatically. You may also use this feature to delete an old email address or add a new one.

Back to Top

* * *

## General Advice

Finally, although HardwareAndTools.com has a very strong Privacy Protection policy on our end, and do their utmost to protect privacy of all visitors, we bear no responsibility for anyone else's conduct with respect to material you transmit. As is true with ANY Internet usage and access to ANY Website, if you are using someone else's computer, or someone else has access to your computer, or spyware is resident on your computer, or you are using a corporate or other "network", it may be possible for that "someone else" or the "network" operator to retrieve copies of Email you sent from the computer and/or to trace the places you have been visiting on the Internet.

Back to Top

* * *

## Amendments

We may amend this Privacy Policy on a prospective basis (i.e., for future visits) at any time by posting a revised policy on our Web site. This policy has been modified as of June 15, 2007. Further, nothing in this Privacy Policy is designed to protect the privacy of visitors whose use of the Company's Website is, in our opinion, or that of our attorneys or affiliates is intended for illegal, improper or abusive purposes, for purposes of marketing or solicitation, or would violate any other terms and conditions relating to use of the Web site.

Back to Top

This policy has been updated as of August 28, 2007

* * *
